saw me the little boy's cucurfor
joy
dressing of in on some candy clothes
special dance
sweet
lucky for key
give me mickey la la la la the ky way up in the sky
comes just from when moonlight goes down
don't be afraid
just remember that i'm waiting for you
you feel so happy
doo
doo happy
happy
you'll never never gonna stop to find the angels first
can you feel so happy
doo
happy
you never ever felt alone
i'm on your side
happy day christmas is once again
bring out your christmas tree in the yellow bro glowing gleaming balls
swan and do it three for
with the way up in the sky
just
lucky
the sun shines comes up
makes me warm
if you lose your restumble and fall
just pick yourself up
one and two and three and four
the ky way up
when the sky comes just for them
when the moonlight goes down
don't be afraid
remember that i'm waiting for you
can you feel so happy
doo doo happy
happy
you're never ever gonna stop to find the angels first
la la la la la la la la la
and they talk about chihu
i tell you i don't know
a quarter of it off
while i was off
sugar
or should i think be
la la la la la la da da da di da da da di da
da da da da
ha ha ha
what would have been you truly come
what you didn't get
what you want being interested in
what would you want
she was a tenant of george youngster
what was this